Guide to the Records of the New York Foundling Hospital 1869-2009 MS 347
New-York Historical Society
- Series V - Records of the St. Agatha Home for Children, 1875-2001
  - Subseries V.5 - St. Agatha Clippings and Photographic Materials, circa 1949-1999
    - St. Agatha - Foundling 125th Anniversary Celebration at St. Agatha - invitation, clippings, and photographic prints, 1994 April 28 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 7)
    - St. Agatha - Exteriors - photographic prints and postcard, 1993, 1998 and undated (pre-1961) (Offsite-box 50, Folder 8)
    - St. Agatha - Photographic prints - 3x5, 4x6, and 5x7 - photographers unknown, circa 1966-1999 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 9)
    - St. Agatha - "Summer of '72" - Photographic prints glued in binder, 1972 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 10)
    - St. Agatha - Photographic prints and contact sheets by James Heffernan and unknown photographers, circa 1979 and undated (Offsite-box 50, Folder 11)
    - St. Agatha - Photographic prints by David Grossman, circa 1980's (Offsite-box 50, Folder 12)
    - St. Agatha - Photographic prints by Claire Yaffa, 1999 and undated (Offsite-box 50, Folder 13)
- Series VI - Foundling Administrators, 1869-2001
  The series consists of one box of materials by or about directors (known variously as Administrators, Superintendents, and Executive Directors) of the New York Foundling Hospital, and members of its Advisory Board. Materials include, but are not limited to, photographic prints, obituaries, correspondence, memos, a dissertation, clippings, and a photocopied diary.
  The first 12 folders document directors who served from 1869-2003, arranged in the order in which they served as directors. Some directors are not represented. These folders are followed by 4 folders documenting the Advisory Board 1869-1970's, arranged chronologically.
  Other materials by or about Foundling administrators may be found throughout this collection. See especially Series I, Minutes, and Series III, Administrative Records, Chronological. In particular, Michael Garber (Executive Director 1997-2003) wrote many reports in Series III. For an oral history interview of Sister Cecilia Schneider, Executive Director 1966-1988, see Series IX - Histories.
  - Sister Irene Fitzgibbon (Founder and Director, 1869-1896) - book of photocopied documents compiled by Joseph D. O'Brien Sr. and Jr., 1990 August (Offsite-box 51, Folder 1)
  - Sister Irene Fitzgibbon - MA Thesis by William Joseph Damroth III, Dept. of Ecclesiastical History, St. Joseph's Seminary, 1993 April (Offsite-box 51, Folder 2)
  - Sister Teresa Vincent (at Foundling 1869-1917; Director 1896-1917) - Photocopy of her diary, 1869 August 16 - October 11 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 3)
  - Sister Anna Michella (Director 1917-1926) - Photographic print (Sister with baby and Foundling cradle), circa 1917-1926 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 4)
  - Sister Dominica (Superintendent 1931-1938) - Photographic prints, press release, correspondence, scrapbook, certificate, circa 1931-1938 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 5)
  - Sister Agnita Miriam (Superintendent 1938-1944) - 4 Photographic prints, circa 1938-1944 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 6)
  - Sister Mary Madeliene (Co-Administrator 1946-1953) - 2 photographic prints, obituary, circa 1946-1953 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 7)
  - Monsignor John Reilly (Co-Administrator 1946-1956) - Obituaries (Offsite-box 51, Folder 8)
  - Sister Marie Catharine Blaine (Administrator circa 1957-1966) - Christmas greetings, mass cards, correspondence, interview transcript, newspaper article, 1947-1965 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 9)
  - Sister Cecilia Schneider (Executive Director 1966-1988) - Correspondence, memos, newsletters, negative, 1967-1989 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 10)
  - Sister Helen Murphy (Executive Director 1988-1996; previously at St. Agatha Home) - Correspondence, photographic prints, memos, dissertation on St. Mary's Shelter, other materials, 1950-1997 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 11)
  - Michael Garber (Executive Director 1997-2003) - Correspondence, memos, 1994-2001 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 12)
  - Advisory Board member John D. Crimmins - Mounted photographic print portrait inscribed to Sister M. Irene, and a copy of a letter to Crimmins, 1896, 1901 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 13)
  - Advisory Board - Correspondence and other materials, 1926, 1933, 1937, 1939 and undated (Offsite-box 51, Folder 14)
  - Advisory Board - photographic prints (group shots) and lists and agendas 1963-1968, circa 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 15)
  - Advisory Board - Photographic prints (portraits), circa 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 16)
  - Advisory Board/Board of Trustees - photographic prints and other materials, circa 1970-1999 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 17)
- Series VII - Foundling Publications - Pamphlets, Appeals, Newsletters, 1909-2009
  The series is divided into two subseries:
  VII.1 - Pamphlets, Appeals, Public Relations Publications, 1909-2007
  VII.2 - Newsletters, 1955-2009
  VII.1 includes pamphlets and other materials produced both for fundraising purposes, and to promote services to clients. The materials promoting services describe either an array of Foundling services or else programs for which no other subseries exists in this collection. Pamphlets for specific programs may be found in Series IV - Centers, Programs and Departments, and Series V - Records of the St. Agatha Home. Materials are arranged chronologically.
  VII.2 includes Foundling newsletters published for external and/or internal audiences. Some newsletters were intended for both groups. VII.2 begins with bound copies of Mater Dei, originally a monthly publication of the Foundling's Association of Foster Parents, although the Association's name was dropped from the banner with the April 1963 issue, possibly reflecting the newsletter's more general distribution and wide-ranging subject matter. Mater Dei published the Foundling's Annual Report as its March issue each year from 1958-1966.
  For other Annual Reports and unbound copies of some of the Mater Dei Annual Report issues, see Series II - Annual Reports. For newsletters from specific programs, see Series IV - Centers, Programs and Departments, and Series V - Records of the St. Agatha Home.
  - Subseries VII.1 - Pamphlets, Appeals, Public Relations Materials, 1909-2007
    - Appeal booklet: "A Little Sketch of a Charity" (2 copies), 1909 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 1)
    - Appeal: "Help us maintain this crib", circa 1925 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 2)
    - Pamphlet: St. Ann's Maternity Hospital, circa 1930-1945 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 3)
    - Pamphlet: St. Mary's Shelter (2 copies), circa 1930-1965 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 4)
    - 2 Appeals, circa 1947-1952 and circa 1948 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 5)
    - Fundraising brochure to finance new building, with appeal by Cardinal Spellman (2 copies), 1956 December 12 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 6)
    - Thank you flier, reporting on Bazaar 1957, circa 1957 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 7)
    - Pamphlets describing services (2 variations), circa 1960-1974 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 8)
    - 15-month calendar/appeal for donations (2 copies), 1969 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 9)
    - Folder describing services, containing materials 1970-1987, circa 1970-1987 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 10)
    - Folder describing services: "Strengthening Child/Parent Relationships" (4 copies, with variations), circa 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 11)
    - Folder describing services, 1975 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 12)
    - Pamphlet describing services, circa 1984 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 13)
    - Pamphlets describing services (2 variations, 5 total pamphlets), circa 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 14)
    - Pamphlets describing history and services (3 variations, 6 total pamphlets), 1994 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 15)
    - Calendar/appeal for donations (2 copies), 1994 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 16)
    - Appeals and public relations materials, circa 1995 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 17)
    - Direct Mail appeal, 1995 December 5 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 18)
    - Public Relations materials, circa 1998 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 19)
    - Pamphlet/appeal describing services, circa 1999 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 20)
    - Pamphlet/appeal, circa 1999-2007 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 21)
    - Booklet describing services, with appeal enclosed, circa 2005 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 22)
    - Public Relations and Development materials, circa 2006 November - 2007 February (Offsite-box 52, Folder 23)
    - Print ad - appeal, circa 2007 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 24)
  - Subseries VII.2 - Newsletters, 1955-2009
    - "Mater Dei" (including Annual Reports), 1955 May - 1960 December (Offsite-box 83, Volume 62)
    - "Mater Dei" (including Annual Reports), 1955 May - 1960 December (Offsite-box 83, Volume 63)
    - "Mater Dei" (including Annual Reports), 1961 January - 1966 April (Offsite-box 83, Volume 64)
    - "Mater Dei" (including Annual Reports), 1961 January - 1966 April (Offsite-box 83, Volume 65)
    - "Mater Dei" (including Annual Reports), 1961 January - 1966 April (Offsite-box 83, Volume 66)
    - "Foundling's Hot Topics" - newsletter for nursery staff, Nos. 1-25, 1960 January - 1962 November (Offsite-box 52, Folder 25)
    - "The Foundling Herald" - newsletter for staff (incomplete run), 1967-1973 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 26)
    - "Professional Newsbriefs" - internal newsletter - 7 issues (incomplete run) - Folder 1 of 4, 1974 December - 1975 May and 1979 January - 1980 June (Offsite-box 52, Folder 27)
    - "Professional Newsbriefs" - newsletter for staff (2 of 4), 1984-1989 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 28)
    - "Professional Newsbriefs" - newsletter for staff (3 of 4), 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 1)
    - "Professional Newsbriefs" - newsletter for staff (4 of 4), 1992-1996 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 2)
    - "Foundling Focus" - newsletter for staff and the public (Folder 1 of 3), 1977-1984 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 3)
    - "Foundling Focus" - newsletter for staff and the public (2 of 3), 1985-2001 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 4)
    - "Foundling Focus" - newsletter for staff and the public (3 of 3), 2003-2008 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 5)
    - "Mission Values in Action" - internal newsletter, 1997 April - 1998 August, and undated (Offsite-box 53, Folder 6)
    - "Applause" - newsletter for staff and volunteers - incomplete run, 1997 October 2 - 2001 March 22 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 7)
    - "NYF News" - newsletter for staff and volunteers - incomplete run, 1998-2000 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 8)
    - "The New York Foundling Executive Director's Report" - quarterly newsletter for staff, volunteers, clients, foster parents (2 issues), 1999, 2000 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 9)
    - "The NYF Research Newsletter" - Vol.1, No.1 (2 copies), 1999 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 10)
    - "NYF - The Manager" - newsletter for managers - Vol.1, No.1 (2 copies), 2000 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 11)
    - Executive Director's Monthly Updates to staff and trustees (email printouts), 2007 May 22 - 2009 April 3 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 12)
- Series VIII - Events, 1875-2007
  The series consists of 3 boxes of materials related to Foundling benefits, galas, parties, and anniversary celebrations, arranged chronologically. These materials are followed by materials related to award presentation ceremonies. Finally, Foundling-sponsored conferences are arranged at the end of the series along with one folder of miscellaneous events. Materials include, but are not limited to, programs, invitations, photographic prints, clippings, and memos.
  - Christmas parties - invitations, programs, appeals, 1875-1948 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 1)
  - Silver Jubilee booklet, 1894 October 11 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 2)
  - Golden Jubilee at Carnegie Hall - booklet with address by Rev. Francis P. Duffy, 1919 April 29 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 3)
  - Golden Jubilee - 2 booklets listing benefactors 1869-1919 and history, and 2 fund-raising pamphlets (Offsite-box 54, Folder 4)
  - Program for Foundling benefit at the Plaza, 1922 April 18 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 5)
  - Program for Foundling benefit at the Plaza, 1925 April 13 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 6)
  - Program for Foundling benefit at Hillyer Hall, 1935 May 15 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 7)
  - 70th Anniversary program - Advisory Board meeting, 1939 October 27 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 8)
  - Invitations to Cardinal Spellman's Christmas parties for children of the Foundling, and Sisters of Charity Christmas cards, 1946-1948 and 1957-1963 (missing 1962) (Offsite-box 54, Folder 9)
  - Benefit concert at Town Hall - Invitation pamphlet and program, 1948 May 19 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 10)
  - 80th Anniversary - invitation, correspondence, photographic prints, clippings, 1949 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 11)
  - 85th Anniversary - clippings, history by Msgr. Reilly, 1954 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 12)
  - 90th Anniversary - Brochure, invitation, photographic prints, flier, clippings, 1959 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 13)
  - Pamphlets for Knights of Columbus Charity Balls, 1960, 1961 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 14)
  - 92nd-95th Annual Bazaar and Open House - 5 fliers, clippings, 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 15)
  - 100th Anniversary - Planning and Public Relations materials, and 100th Anniversary Bazaar flier stuck to P.R. correspondence, 1968 September 4 - 1969 October 3 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 16)
  - 100th Anniversary - programs, invitations and other materials for various events, 1969 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 17)
  - 100th Anniversary - correspondence from Mayor Lindsay and Cardinal Cooke (originals), Richard Nixon and Nelson Rockefeller (copies), misc. other materials, 1969 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 1)
  - 100th Anniversary - Photographic prints, 1969 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 2)
  - 100th Anniversary - clippings, 1969 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 3)
  - Program for Afro-American Cultural Exhibit sponsored by Foundling, 1969 March 23 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 4)
  - Programs and invitations for Catholic Institute of the Food Industry Man of the Year Award dinner dances to benefit Foundling 1980-1988 (missing 1984) (Offsite-box 55, Folder 5)
  - 125th Anniversary Mass at St. Patrick's - photographic prints, liturgy (2 copies), invitation, other materials, 1994 January 9 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 6)
  - 125th Anniversary Gala - invitation, program, booklets (2 copies), photographic prints, correspondence from Cardinal O'Connor, President Clinton, Governor Cuomo, 1994 October 25 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 7)
  - 125th Anniversary birthday party at 590 Avenue of the Americas - 1994 November 11 and 15 - invitation, planning memos, correspondence, other materials, 1994 July 19 - November (Offsite-box 55, Folder 8)
  - 125th Anniversary birthday party at 590 Avenue of the Americas - Photographic prints, 1994 November 11 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 9)
  - 125th Anniversary exhibition and reception at MetLife - photographic prints, program, invitation, memos, correspondence from Mayor Giuliani and other materials, 1994 September 1 - December 16 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 10)
  - 125th Anniversary - events at NYU and City Council proclamation, 1994 September 19 - October 25 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 11)
  - 125th Anniversary - miscellaneous events and materials - programs, memos, photographic prints, booklet, correspondence, invitations, fliers, calendar, 1993 November 23 - 1995 June (Offsite-box 55, Folder 12)
  - 125th Anniversary - clippings, 1994 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 13)
  - Sister Mary Irene Fitzgibbon Place - street naming request and ceremony - photographic prints, program, memos, minutes, other materials, 1994-1997 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 14)
  - 1996 Gala - 2 programs, invitations, photographic prints, 1996 October 7 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 1)
  - 1997 Gala - 2 programs, invitation, 1997 November 13 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 2)
  - 1997 Gala - photographic prints, 1997 November 13 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 3)
  - 1998 Gala - 2 programs, 2 books, 1998 December 1 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 4)
  - 1999 Benefit Theatre Party - invitation, 1999 June 10 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 5)
  - Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation Dinner - invitation, 2004 October 21 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 6)
  - 135th Anniversary dinner at the Dakota - 2 programs, 2004 November 9 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 7)
  - 135th Anniversary reception at Rubin Museum - 2 programs, circa 2004 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 8)
  - 2007 Gala at Villard Mansion - program, 2007 February 12 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 9)
  - Award presentations - photographic prints, circa 1977-1998 anda undated (Offsite-box 56, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous award presentation documents, 1988, 1997-2001 and undated (Offsite-box 56, Folder 11)
  - Legacy of Hope Award - invitations, programs, press releases, memos, other materials, 1995, 1997, 1999, 2000, 2002 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 12)
  - Programs for a child care symposium and child care workshop, hosted by Foundling, and follow-up memo, 1961 and circa 1961 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 13)
  - Foundling-sponsored professional conferences and training programs - programs, registration forms, 1993-1998 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 14)
  - Training and Development Institute - course registration pamphlets (3 different pamphlets), circa 1997-1999 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 15)
  - Foundling-sponsored professional conference on substance abuse - programs and registration materials (2 copies), 1999 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous events - photographic prints, ephemera, 1992, 2000 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 17)
- Series IX - Histories of the Foundling, 1869-1994
  The series consists of one box of writings on the history of the Foundling, composed by various authors, 1869-2004, arranged chronologically by date of composition. The series also contains one audiotape of an oral history, and its transcription.
  - Histories, 1869-1899 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 1)
  - Histories, 1917-1939 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 2)
  - Histories, 1941-1956 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 3)
  - Histories, circa 1958-1999 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 4)
  - Oral history interview of Sister Cecilia Schneider - audiotape and transcript, 1993 November 8 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 5)
  - "A Legacy of Hope" history of the Foundling by Sister Anne Courtney, circa 1994 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 6)
- Series X - Sisters of Charity and Archdiocese of New York, 1900-2006
  Nuns of the Sisters of Charity founded, administered, and worked at the Foundling and the St. Agatha Home, in the Archdiocese of New York. The series consists of four folders of materials on the Sisters of Charity and its founder St. Elizabeth Seton, and one bronze medal of Elizabeth Seton. The folders are followed by five folders of materials on five of the archbishops who have led the Archdiocese of New York, arranged chronologically.
  Materials include, but are not limited to, pamphlets, memos, correspondence, photographic prints and clippings, and periodicals. Periodicals are housed in a separate oversized (OS) box, noted in the container list.
  Two volumes on the Sisters of Charity may be found in Series XVII, Published Books. A volume by Frances Cardinal Spellman may also be found in Series XVII. Additional correspondence and photographic prints of the Archbishops of New York may be found throughout other series in the collection.
  - Brochures, booklets, pamphlets and information sheets re: Elizabeth Seton, circa 1950-1997 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 1)
  - Bronze medal commemorating Elizabeth Seton, separated to Box 77, circa 1975-2005 (Offsite-box 77)
  - Sisters of Charity - lists of sisters missioned to N.Y. Foundling Hospital, circa 1977-2006 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 2)
  - "175 Years of Presence": booklet about Sisters of Charity, 1992 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 3)
  - Sisters of Charity miscellaneous - invitations, photograph, clippings, booklet, mass, circa 1983-1997 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 4)
  - Archbishop Michael Augustine Corrigan (1885-1902) - pastoral letter, 1900 April 21 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 5)
  - Cardinal Spellman (Archbishop 1939-1967) - photographic print, correspondence, masses, 25th Anniversary commemorative book. 2 commemorative issues of Catholic News separated to OS 1, Folder 6, circa 1940-1966 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 6)
  - Cardinal Cooke (Archbishop 1968-1983) - photographic prints, clippings. 1 commemorative issue of Catholic News separated to OS 1, Folder 6., circa 1968-1979 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 7)
  - Cardinal O'Connor (Archbishop 1984-2000) - photographic prints, clippings, circa 1989-2000 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 8)
  - Cardinal Egan (Archbishop 2000-2009) - Correspondence, 2001 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 9)
- Series XI - Visual Materials, circa 1880-2005
  The series contains four boxes of visual materials representing the New York Foundling Hospital circa 1880-2005.
  The first three boxes contain mainly photographic prints, but there are a few photomechanical reproductions and drawings as well. Images include building exteriors, events and people. Most photographs were created for publicity purposes. The fourth box consists of negatives and positive transparencies depicting a Foundling exhibition, mounted circa 1969-1994, tracing the organization's history in photographs and other visual materials. Most of the images in these transparencies and negatives exist in other formats (photographic prints etc.) in the first three boxes of this series, or in other series in the collection.
  Photographic prints are arranged roughly chronologically. At each new main location of the Foundling, exteriors are arranged first, followed by interiors grouped in folders by subject. The series concludes with 7 folders of material by the photographer Claire Yaffa, including photographic prints, printed photo essays, and related material such as consent forms.
  Hundreds of additional photographic prints can be found in other series in the collection, especially Series IV, V, and VI. This distribution throughout the collection reflects the original order in which the materials were arranged at the Foundling. A book about the Foundling including photographs by Claire Yaffa is part of Series XVII, Published Books.
  - 17 East 12th St. (location of Foundling, 1869) exterior - retouched photographic print, undated (Offsite-box 59, Folder 1)
  - 3 Washington Square North (location of Foundling 1870-1873) exteriors - 3 photographic prints, undated (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
  - 68th Street buildings exterior - view North from 67th Street - vintage print, circa 1880 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 3)
  - 68th St. building exteriors - artist's rendition, circa 1882 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 4)
  - 68th Street building exteriors - view NW along 68th Street, from a height near 68th and 3rd - 3 vintage prints, mounted, circa 1882-1896 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 5)
  - St. John's Children's Hospital exterior - view NW from above 3rd Avenue El, circa 1882-1896 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 6)
  - Hillyer Memorial Auditorium exterior - corner of 68th and Lexington - view NE from SW corner of 68th and Lex - 1 vintage print, mounted, circa 1900-1915 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 7)
  - St. Ann's exterior - head-on view facing North - photographic print, circa 1916-1958 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 8)
  - St. Irene's (corner of 68th and 3rd)- exterior - view NE from 68th St. (2 vintage prints); view NW from under 3rd Avenue El (reprint), undated (Offsite-box 59, Folder 9)
  - 68th St. buildings exterior - view NE from SW corner of 68th and Lexington - 2 prints, 1958 and circa 1940's (Offsite-box 59, Folder 10)
  - 68th St. Exterior - Main building and Grotto - 3 prints, circa 1930-1958 and circa 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 11)
  - 68th St. complex of buildings exteriors - 17 5.25 x 7.25 color prints, circa 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 12)
  - 68th St. complex of buildings exteriors - 12 3.5 x 4.5 black and white prints, circa 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 13)
  - Street plan 66-69th Streets, Park-Third Avenues (oversize), undated (Offsite-box OS 1, Folder 1)